[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What four words end the first two lines of this famous Christmas poem ?\n\nTwas the night before Christmas, when all through the house\nNot a creature was stirring, ___ ___ __ _____.", "correct_answer": "not even a mouse.", "incorrect_answers": ["not even a grouse.", "not even Juliet Prowse.", "not even a louse."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tarsals are located in what part of the body?", "correct_answer": "Foot or eyelid", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Elbows", "Hands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jack Ryan, one of the main characters in The Hunt for Red October, was a graduate from the U.S. Naval Academy. What year did he graduate?", "correct_answer": "1972", "incorrect_answers": ["1974", "1968", "1970"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Benjamin Martin melt into musket balls in the movie The Patriot?", "correct_answer": "Thomas toy lead soldiers", "incorrect_answers": ["Bricks", "Ink", "Gabriels toy lead soldiers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which sign is considered to be most lucky and powerful?", "correct_answer": "Dragon", "incorrect_answers": ["Rooster", "Ox", "Fox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not a property of light?", "correct_answer": "Viscosity", "incorrect_answers": ["Frequency", "Polarization", "Intensity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 100 people, how many would live in substandard housing?", "correct_answer": "80", "incorrect_answers": ["20", "40", "60"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are you lookin at, Butthead? was a question asked in what movie?", "correct_answer": "Back to the Future", "incorrect_answers": ["Beavis and Butthead do America", "Old School", "Elf"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Mrs. Doubtfire, Miranda decides to let the court overturn their decision on Daniel, which in turn, allows him to spend every day with his children. What drives her to this decision?", "correct_answer": "She sees him acting on a television show.", "incorrect_answers": ["He stops drinking and becomes a responsible parent.", "He remarries and seems to have a better grip on life and his decision making", "He gets a full time job as an airline pilot."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the paperboys name in the 2006 movie The Benchwarmers?", "correct_answer": "Clark", "incorrect_answers": ["It wasnt mentioned", "Bob", "Billy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From which language do we get the word tattoo?", "correct_answer": "Tahitian", "incorrect_answers": ["Tongan", "Maori", "Marshallese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie For Your Eyes Only, the so-called countess Lisl von Schlaf, comes from which city?", "correct_answer": "Manchester", "incorrect_answers": ["Dublin", "Glasgow", "Swansea"]}]